<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Post-first-versions on </title>
    <link>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Post-first-versions on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cycle Compounds biggest results. Magical beans
</title>
      <link>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/dct-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/dct-stack/</guid>
      <description>First effects of DCT stack  Promotes soon recovering following fun and whole testosterone recovery.
 During cycle therapy enhances to most roid gains.
 Allows to protect healthful range of testosterone.
 Offers accurate managing of each combo.
 Holds excellent sex interest during the long steroid use.
 Covers the rational muscle builders, kicks risks aside.
 Guards from gynaecomastia while you apply big amounts of androgens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Side Effects of Deca Durabolin
</title>
      <link>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/ndd-04441/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/ndd-04441/</guid>
      <description>Drawbacks of ND steroid Nortestosterone Decanoate can be the optimal choice, specially if user need to gain huge muscle mass fast. Deca Durabolin still remains on a selection of greatest functional, beneficial pumpers. Around 50 years before Nandrolonum accomplished remarkable fame.
Casting couple of androgenic roids to your stack, something like Strombaject, user will certainly build his 1st 16 lbs within 60 days. Looking into varied traits, one can&amp;rsquo;t get substitute for Nor-19-testosterone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brilliant NPP combinations
</title>
      <link>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/npp-04348/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/npp-04348/</guid>
      <description>Classic 19-Nortestosterone Phenyl stacks Sustanon 350 accompanied by 17-phenylpropionate defeats lady&amp;rsquo;s PRL. Cabergolinum or maybe Winny-V will easily clear prolactin issues.
Combine with Turinabol &amp;amp; Omnadren, to actually get output bonus. Unite Durabolin alongside Dehydromethyltestosteron, in cases aggressive muscular increase is your choice.
Test Blend combos allows to receive maximum out from 19-Norandrostenolone Phenyl. The muscular increases from correct roid combo feel tough, also hold longer.
Reasonable trouble-free limit in 10d could be 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Main effects of Winstrol Depot use
</title>
      <link>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/win-04157/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/win-04157/</guid>
      <description>First effects of Strombaject use Best Androstanazole point: weight-loss, quality or pumping stacks. This AS should eliminate excess weight, define 6 pack, store muscular tissue at strict daily diet.
 Provides toned appearance, draws lean abs.
 Enhances quickness &amp;amp; resistance.
 Rushes metabolic level.
 Supports muscles, removes weight.
 Expels excessive fluid, excludes watery weight.
  Estazol Gym Injects Shreded looks, remarkable pumping plus total lack of gynaecomastia making lots of steroiders happy but Winnie Anabolic Injects - epic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nerobol candies with Testosterone Mix
</title>
      <link>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/1-dbl-1-sus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/1-dbl-1-sus/</guid>
      <description>Nerobol as candies description Don&amp;rsquo;t u understand why exactly D-Bol consistently popular now? Many guys emphasize exceptional results of Anabolin mass drugs, rest repeat that roid is messy and intense. Such strong gear will pay u with bigmuscle 4 almost nothing, efficiently gets newcomer to the industry of body tweaking.
Methandienone - widely known muscle growing master of anabolic business. Today so what helped Dianabol to be the first rate?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dianabol anabolic tablets users guide
</title>
      <link>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/dbl-04052/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/dbl-04052/</guid>
      <description>D Bol steroid tablets users guide Nerobol - the notable muscle improving veteran of pharma industry. Today what empowers Dianabol remain greatest? His honest review is affordable, muscle growing and variable. Useful, tho D Bol is easy like hammer.
The bulking results are equally proper to professional builder &amp;amp; to a starter. Small cost, stunning result allow him to confidently stand on the peak. Dehydromethyltestosterone achieved fame in the underground gym, around power cages, furthermore within bodybuilding community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use TP anabolic - Newbies corner
</title>
      <link>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/tep-04876/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/tep-04876/</guid>
      <description>How to apply TP anabolic? For all AAS combinations, Steroid Hormone grew to good ground. The hormone solo work poorly, this is ridiculous to pray for quality gains using hormone alone.
Prop of Testosterone steroid injection - most suitable for your first stack, works very fast, stores fluids badly, is cost-effective. Separate 2 hundred milligrams per 1 week and stick with the same portions alone at alternate day, get started through smaller quantity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Additional Cycle Medications work?
</title>
      <link>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/1-cyc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/1-cyc/</guid>
      <description>How Additional Cycle Medications stuff work Have U ever had accident drop during cycle, draw the bag of sudden troubles? Why one should consume more drugs on cycle even it feels so great with AS? BB require additional products to gain musclegrowing extreme and also escape sides.
DCT secure roiders stones &amp;amp; handle unwanted formation of luteotropin. DCT allows one to speed up stacks to maximum. When u expect to win maximum benefit out of anabolic steroids find right Supplementary Products first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exclusive summary. Mass Tablets user reactions
</title>
      <link>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/bodybuilders-candies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/bodybuilders-candies/</guid>
      <description>Bodybuilders Candies review Tablet insures - any time party blows, one might return on track around the night or maybe few, come off fast. Thanks to dreadful experiences that unsophisticated guys reveal it&amp;rsquo;s ridiculous 2 panic. Pills are comfortable, difficult to miscount, bodybuilder don&amp;rsquo;t actually have to merge and stuff a ned.
Endocrine system unavoidably eliminates the T hormone creation, since cannot realize if you loaded some ester or else swallowed pill.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After Cycle Drugs for athletes. Impacts of PCT
</title>
      <link>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/pct/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/pct/</guid>
      <description>PCT Products abuse Ending of usage will hit in the nuts and viciously trash muscle. Following solo cycle you don&amp;rsquo;t require PCT - this advice delusional nonsense. When hormone level isn&amp;rsquo;t promptly forced in place your gear cannot succeed.
HPG does not recognize the labeling of Steroid Juice - the combination you&amp;rsquo;re taking or taking solo, soft or maybe hard. Body shouldn&amp;rsquo;t question what steroid you implement - Metenolone Enanthate, Test Mix - it identifies high test and stops to generate inner hormone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Popular Tamifen drug usage
</title>
      <link>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/popular-tamifen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/popular-tamifen/</guid>
      <description>Popular Tamifen drug stack Pack forty milligrams at first. Maintain improved dosage a few times. Lower to 30 and keep at a few days. From the 8 day you can calm down a tad.
User could calmly continue roid plan. You don&amp;rsquo;t need to reduce the dosage of aromatizing bolins, quit roid cycle whenever titties seem itchy. Nolva amount should get larger if bodybuilder made mistake and unnecessary estrogen overdose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mysteries of athletics accomplishments.  What can Nortestosterone Phenylpropionate steroid do?
</title>
      <link>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/nortestosterone-phenyl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/nortestosterone-phenyl/</guid>
      <description>Cutting effects of 19-Nortestosterone Phenyl steroid Nortestosterone Phenyl gives you good preciseness for managing of your routine, the drug is fast ester. For bodybuilder who prefer to control usage NPP Deca really is the speeding advantage.
At recent years 19-Norandrostenolone Phenyl began to ultimately crowd out typical Decanoate. Starter, look at 17-phenylpropionate firstly, you easily recognize the exceptional perks. Once you got unlucky, Nandrolone Phenyl may give you a good bonus - will be easier to stop and so rapidly free your plasma.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts and comments. Nandrolone AS profile
</title>
      <link>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/nandrolone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/nandrolone/</guid>
      <description>Whats Norandrostenolon anabolic? Nortestosteronum is master of doping game, valuable AS meant for therapy of severe injuries plus the bulking. Oestrenolone runs softly, he almost does not transform and is a lousy androgen, but the dynamic wow-effect from the use is infrequent. Inject won&amp;rsquo;t pour fluids back &amp;amp; forth, drug provide the serious meat , Norandrostenolone&amp;rsquo;s capacity is thoroughly tested.
19-Nortestosterone doping is manufactured as only few esters: a rapid and long life style.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gym Injects for bulking.  Impacts of anabolic steroids
</title>
      <link>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/injects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/injects/</guid>
      <description>How to take AS Juice stuff? Even if they may hold specific quantity of the poisoning, AS Pills remain irreplaceable, often needed and also extremely efficient. Sust-250 can be real machine of efficacy with out the substitutes. It is tricky for the unskilled chemists, when unaware smartheads encourage to incorporate just steroid tablets.
Bodybuilders Shots - an indispensable device on menu of any educated muscle builder, no matter what advisors suppose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Steroid Shots works?  Opening practices of bodybuilding
</title>
      <link>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/roids-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/roids-do/</guid>
      <description>What does Roids do? Testosterone alters basic nitric levels into an effective way. AS build for multiple sport goals ideal conditions.
There is no basic reaction lacking a natural testosterone, also no purpose to receive desired gains. Sports supplements only give a resource to your physique, supports routine. Muscles start growing while a person&amp;rsquo;s physique provides specific hormones.
Substances actually utilised to cure anaemia, skin injury, intense fatigue, dystrophy. Anabolic substance raises metabolic process - regenerates muscular tissue and heals physical traumas, bone injuries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drawbacks of Test Blend steroid.  How you can quit hesitating and begin loving oneself
</title>
      <link>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/sust-anabolic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/sust-anabolic/</guid>
      <description>Problems from Sustanon 350 injections Start out Z-Toremifene tablets 7 days after Testosterone Blend halting, you can protect your main results. If roid cycle involves Tren Hex, take Dyneric. Right off avoid the post-cycle loss by using Spiropent (Clen) drugs.
Sus 250 decreases body&amp;rsquo;s testosterone, this means you have to boost testosterone levels. Starters who typically ignore PCT Support easily shed the results. At the finishing, anti-estrogens - builder&amp;rsquo;s companions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mysteries of athletics achievements.  T Hormone anabolic injection
</title>
      <link>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/testosterone/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/testosterone/</guid>
      <description>First effects of Testosterone usage Testoenant starts action late, however will provide fantastic bulks for certain. Testosterone 17beta-Enanthate juice - diesel energy amongst Test types, 2 shots a week may be decent to keep a high concentration of the hormone.
Propionate of Testosterone can satisfies lovers of high speeds, juice allow one benefit on start. Propionate of Test AAS goes into action soon, perfect form of T injections for those that lazy to wait for first effect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete guidance. Testosterone Ethanate steroid mix
</title>
      <link>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/testoenant/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/testoenant/</guid>
      <description>Pros of Testoenant steroid Perfect muscle definition, power and fat-burning can gain from the cycle with Tren. Stanozolol going to be its best companion for geting more rigidity and also fat-burning.
To receive real meat, supply excess steroids - Boldenone Undec. In case you desire an ultra mass growing, stack together with Dbol will actively work with bulk development.
Testosterone heptoate drawbacks Start off Tamoxifene 1 week following Testosterone Enanthate anabolic shot quitting, you&amp;rsquo;ll hold all the increases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suspension of Test AAS stacks.  What is essential to fulfill the end goal?
</title>
      <link>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/test-suspension/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/test-suspension/</guid>
      <description>Suspension of Testosterone perks When you choose the ultra bulking, mix along with Nerobol must distinctively work towards the mass enhancement. To gain raw muscle mass, no watery weight, put strong anabolic steroids - Trenbolone.
Oral-Winstrol shall be his best companion fat-burning and also 4 additional firmness. Amazing force, fat-burning, mass precision should inevitably receive out of steroid combination with Finaject.
Suspension of Test steroid guide No matter what wiseacres think about Androgen AAS, he&amp;rsquo;s a proud papa of all steroids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to continue the proper journey.  Cyp of Test anabolic side effects
</title>
      <link>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/cypionate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/cypionate/</guid>
      <description>Sides of Test Cypionate shots Testosterone Cyclopentanepropionate or Enth are types and not different substances, good PCT Therapy is recommended. If injected Test Cyp, wait six days, then get Clen and Torem for 1 month.
Antiestrogens are BB&amp;rsquo;s buddies on the finish line. Novices which generally neglect PCT Therapy stupidly drop the results. Anyone should increase hormone production, as Anabolic Hormone strongly disturbs body&amp;rsquo;s testosterone.
Start off Таmoр on one week following Depo-Testosterone halting and you will retain your main increases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to end Testosterone P cycle.  What is crucial to attain the purpose?
</title>
      <link>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/propionate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/propionate/</guid>
      <description>Propionate safe dose Split up 200 milligram to weeks period &amp;amp; use portion any other day. Test Prop - best for first cycle, acts in a short time, preserves liquid poorly, inexpensive.
Human Testosterone became a strong base for all anabolic steroid combinations. The Testosterone work weakly solo, it&amp;rsquo;s ignorant using it separately but expect excellent improvements.
1 gram in acting product for 1 week would be proper boundary to any muscle fan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AS Pills best cycle. What&#39;s the profit of these types of substances
</title>
      <link>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/xplode-bomb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/xplode-bomb/</guid>
      <description>AS Injections xplode bomb You sometimes read that that&amp;rsquo;s ample to put injects into needle, ingest the capsule. To keep workout process like it has to, you have to carefully watch the blood changes and bodily testosterone, continue monitoring.
Trenbolone Hex pick out extremely devoted builders. Select Oral Winstrol and merge that with Eth of Test for the base incase you wish to shed the unneeded bodyweight. Inject Trenbolone A to brake limitations, AS should pack a person with the nice muscle and also great charge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nerobol capsules - bodybuilder&#39;s candy
</title>
      <link>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/nerobol-capsules/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/nerobol-capsules/</guid>
      <description>Side effects of Nerobol capsules Absolute best and extremely cheap - this is the major asset which dignifies this nontrivial AAS. At same check unthinkable 2 find any convincing alternatives. Thais going to carry the top score many years, with stack of features.
Dehydromethyltestosteron - bodybuilder&amp;rsquo;s candy, gear pumped hundreds thousands of sexy athletes, half of them grew self confidence. A1-Dehydromethyltesteroneperforms wonders with skinny and drained body. Stenolon gym drugs are not quite cruel.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>