<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pct on </title>
    <link>https://icedseat.github.io/tags/pct/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pct on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://icedseat.github.io/tags/pct/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Popular Tamifen drug usage
</title>
      <link>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/popular-tamifen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/popular-tamifen/</guid>
      <description>Popular Tamifen drug stack Pack forty milligrams at first. Maintain improved dosage a few times. Lower to 30 and keep at a few days. From the 8 day you can calm down a tad.
User could calmly continue roid plan. You don&amp;rsquo;t need to reduce the dosage of aromatizing bolins, quit roid cycle whenever titties seem itchy. Nolva amount should get larger if bodybuilder made mistake and unnecessary estrogen overdose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Popular Tamifen drug usage.
</title>
      <link>https://icedseat.github.io/post/popular-tamifen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icedseat.github.io/post/popular-tamifen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;popular-tamifen-drug-stack&#34;&gt;Popular Tamifen drug stack&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pack forty milligrams at first. Maintain improved dosage a few times.
Lower to 30 and keep at a few days. From the 8 day you can calm down a tad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;User could calmly continue roid plan. You don&amp;rsquo;t need to reduce the
dosage of aromatizing bolins, quit roid cycle whenever titties seem itchy.
Nolva amount should get larger if bodybuilder made mistake and unnecessary
estrogen overdose. One should respond urgently to not become woman!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Steroid Shots works?  Opening practices of bodybuilding
</title>
      <link>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/roids-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icedseat.github.io/post-first-version/roids-do/</guid>
      <description>What does Roids do? Testosterone alters basic nitric levels into an effective way. AS build for multiple sport goals ideal conditions.
There is no basic reaction lacking a natural testosterone, also no purpose to receive desired gains. Sports supplements only give a resource to your physique, supports routine. Muscles start growing while a person&amp;rsquo;s physique provides specific hormones.
Substances actually utilised to cure anaemia, skin injury, intense fatigue, dystrophy. Anabolic substance raises metabolic process - regenerates muscular tissue and heals physical traumas, bone injuries.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>